Hey, where did all the fish go?
I don’t know
Hello, my name is Olafur. I am an artist
and I made a work of art called Earth Speakr
Let me show it to you
With the artwork, you can make a tree talk
You can make the sky cry, a rock on the
maybe it's like, screaming at you
and the flowers, they can be smiling
You can really say anything you want to say
or tell us to do about
how do we make the planet safe for the future
You could consider making me in more climate friendly materials
Just a thought!
And then I promise I will take that and try to deliver it
to the politicians, to the people in power so they listen to you
It’s simple to use
You will see how it mirrors your face and your expressions
Then think about what you want to say
You record your message
I don’t want plastic inside my fish!
And then you place it where you want to have it
Your message then can join a community
of other messages
Soon your message will be in the world
And if you have Earth Speakr on your phone,
you can see other kids’ messages, and they can see yours
in augmented reality
See, each of these glass spheres is actually a message
So you can zoom in when you find it and tap on it, and then you can hear the message
You can pick your favourite message and then share it with your friends
And you can make your own and send it off
You can tell your parents or a grown-up friend
to look at the messages on earthspeakr.art
Adults cannot make their own messages; this is just for kids
But they can make really cool Loud Speakrs
on a map
and the more Loud Speakrs, the more grown-ups will also see your messages
Now everyone can see your Loud Speakr in augmented reality
through the Earth Speakr app
Earth Speakr is for you
it’s for your friends, it’s for everyone
and it’s about having fun, being creative, playing
But it’s also about saying, what do we need to do for the planet?